{
    "subject": "resource/GCstar",
    "predicate": "ontology/license",
    "object": "resource/GNU_General_Public_License",
    "human_readable": "The license of GCstar is GNU General Public License.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9420127868652344,
            "question": "What does the GNU General Public License allow users to do with GCstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8981216549873352,
            "question": "Does the GNU General Public License require attribution for modifications to GCstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6890465021133423,
            "question": "What type of license is used for GCstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6719947457313538,
            "question": "Under which license can GCstar be used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.645993709564209,
            "question": "What is the full name of the license used by GCstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.574617862701416,
            "question": "What is the significance of using an open-source license like the GNU General Public License?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4969850182533264,
            "question": "Are there any restrictions on using GCstar under its license?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22456303238868713,
            "question": "Is GCstar open-source software?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2053307294845581,
            "question": "Who can modify and distribute GCstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15874527394771576,
            "question": "Can commercial software be developed using GCstar's code?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The license of GCstar is GNU General Public License.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7411_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who can modify and distribute GCstar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7411_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is GCstar open-source software?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7411_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any restrictions on using GCstar under its license?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7411_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7411_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"GCstar is released under the GNU General Public License\" and \"Released under a GNU General Public License (GPL), GCstar is free and open source.\" Therefore, the statement that the license of GCstar is GNU General Public License is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}